xiaomitoday.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy - XiaomiToday

**This policy was last updated  ** **on October 31** **,** **  2018.** 

At XiaomiToday, we want you to enjoy and benefit from our websites and online services in the safest way possible. That’s why we have implemented fair information practices designed to protect your privacy. Our privacy policy is applicable to XiaomiToday, and XiaomiToday affiliates and subsidiaries whose websites, mobile applications and other online services are directly linked (the “Sites”). 

The privacy policy describes the kinds of information we may gather during your visit to these Sites, how we use your information, when we might disclose your personally identifiable information, and how you can manage your information. 

This privacy policy does not apply to Sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link or who may link to us. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third party websites. 

**By visiting our Sites, you are accepting the practices described in our privacy policy, including our use of cookies and similar online tools. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy, please do not use the Sites.**  

We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our privacy policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this privacy policy retroactively or to personally identifiable information already in our possession, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments and seek your consent for such use. 

## **What Information Is Collected?**  

We collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Sites: non-personally identifiable information and personally identifiable information. Non-personally identifiable information does not individually identify you, but it may include tracking and usage information about your general location, demographics, use of the Sites and the Internet. Personally identifiable information is any information that can individually identify you and includes: your name, address, phone number, and email address, or non-personally identifiable information that has been linked to such personally identifiable information.   

## **Personally Identifiable Information**  

As a general matter, you can browse the Sites without submitting your personally identifiable information to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may supply us with your personally identifiable information, including when you subscribe to our publications, newsletters, and other content; register for a Site or any part thereof; complete a poll or participate in market research; enter a contest; upload content; or when you seek employment at XiaomiToday. 

## **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  

When you interact with the Sites, we may collect certain information that does not identify you individually (“non-personally identifiable information” or “non-PII”), such as demographic data; information about your computer, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Sites, including IP address, general location information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language, and other transactional information. 

We may also collect information about your use of the Sites, including your search terms and search results, and additional “traffic data” such as time of access, date of access, software crash reports, session identification number, access times, and referring website addresses. Our servers may automatically keep an activity log of your use of our Sites. In addition to non-identifiable individual information, we may collect aggregate data regarding the use of the Sites. 

## **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information from** **  or t** **hrough Social Media Sites**  

In addition, when you interact with any XiaomiToday page or account on a social media platform, such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram, we may collect the personally identifiable information that you make available to us on that page or account including your social media account ID. However, we will comply with the privacy policies of the corresponding social media platform and we will only collect and store such personally identifiable information that we are permitted to collect by those social media platforms. With your consent, we also may share information about your activities, including what you view on the Sites, with that social network’s users. 

## **Collection of Your Source IP Address/Location Information**  

We collect and store your device’s source IP address which may disclose the general location of your device at the time you access the Sites. Advertisements and certain content may be directed to you as a result of this data. 

**Information f** **ro** **m o** **ther  ** **s** **ources** : We may supplement the information we collect with information from third parties or collected offline and add it to your account information. This information may include but is not limited to, demographic information, additional contact information, group affiliations, occupational information, and educational background. 

## **How Do We Use Your Information?**  

We use the information we learn from you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Sites, including to: 

  * Provide you with the content, products and services you request 
  * Post your user-generated content to our Sites as you request 
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies 
  * Communicate with you about your comment to a story or topic 
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Sites, including providing you recommendations based on your preferences 
  * Send you newsletters, offers and promotions for our products and services, third party products and services, or special events by e-mail, text, or other another medium 
  * Provide you with advertising including advertising based on your activity on our Sites or activity on third party sites and applications 
  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations 
  * Detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal 
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Sites and their purchasing patterns 

We may use the information from one portion of the Sites on other portions of Sites in our network of Sites, all of which are owned and operated by XiaomiToday, and we may combine information gathered from multiple portions of the Sites into a single user record. We also may use or combine information that we collect offline or we collect or receive from third-party sources for many reasons, including to enhance, expand, and check the accuracy of our records. Additionally, data collected from a particular browser or device may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which such data was collected. 

## **Who Can See Your Information?**  

We will not disclose your personally identifiable information collected from the Sites to any organizations not part of XiaomiToday or its subsidiaries or related entities, except as described in this privacy policy. 

## **Third-Party Agents**  

We have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, hosting, content syndication, content management tools, social media integration, marketing, analytics, billing and customer service. These entities may have access to personally identifiable information if needed to perform their functions. If such access is required, the third parties will be obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personally identifiable information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Sites. Below is a list of Third-party scripts or SDKS that may be used on XiaomiToday: 

## **Jetpack  ** **Plugin**  

## **Ads**  

**Data Used** : The following information (made available from the visitor’s browser) is collected and sent to Automattic’s Demand Partners: IP address, geographical data (derived from the IP address), user agent, operating system, device type, unique user ID (randomly generated identifier), current URL, and IAB (Interactive Advertising Bureau) interest category. Log data (IP address, geographical data, user agent, operating system, device type) is stored for 30 days. The unique user ID is stored in cookies and is retained for 1 year. 

**Activity Tracked** : Ad impressions, video-related events (i.e. pause, mute, 100% plays, etc.) or errors, and ad click events. Various cookies are used for the following purposes: delivering targeted advertisements to specific visitors, storing user identifiers, and collecting anonymous ad platform stats. 

## **Contact Form**  

**Data Used** : If Akismet is enabled on the site, the contact form submission data — IP address, user agent, name, email address, website, and message — is submitted to the Akismet service (also owned by Automattic) for the sole purpose of spam checking. The actual submission data is stored in the database of the site on which it was submitted and is emailed directly to the owner of the form (i.e. the site author who published the page on which the contact form resides). This email will include the submitter’s IP address, timestamp, name, email address, website, and message. 

**Data Synced** : Post and post metadata associated with a user’s contact form submission. If Akismet is enabled on the site, the IP address and user agent originally submitted with the comment are synced, as well, as they are stored in post meta. 

## **Google Analytics**  

**Data Used** : Please refer to the appropriate Google Analytics documentation for the specific type of data it collects. For sites running WooCommerce (also owned by Automattic) and this feature simultaneously and having all purchase tracking explicitly enabled, purchase events will send Google Analytics the following information: order number, product id and name, product category, total cost, and quantity of items purchased. Google Analytics does offer IP anonymization, which can be enabled by the site owner. 

**Activity Tracked** : This feature sends page view events (and potentially video play events) over to Google Analytics for consumption. For sites running WooCommerce-powered stores, some additional events are also sent to Google Analytics: shopping cart additions and removals, product listing views and clicks, product detail views, and purchases. Tracking for each specific WooCommerce event needs to be enabled by the site owner. 

## **Gravatar** ** ** **Hovercards**  

**Data Used:**  This feature will send a hash of the user’s email address (if logged in to the site or WordPress.com — or if they submitted a comment on the site using their email address that is attached to an active Gravatar profile) to the Gravatar service (also owned by Automattic) in order to retrieve their profile image. 

## **Jetpack Comments**  

**Data Used:**  Commenter’s name, email address, and site URL (if provided via the comment form), timestamp, and IP address. Additionally, a jetpack.wordpress.com IFrame receives the following data: WordPress.com blog ID attached to the site, ID of the post on which the comment is being submitted, commenter’s local user ID (if available), commenter’s local username (if available), commenter’s site URL (if available), MD5 hash of the commenter’s email address (if available), and the comment content. If Akismet (also owned by Automattic) is enabled on the site, the following information is sent to the service for the sole purpose of spam checking: commenter’s name, email address, site URL, IP address, and user agent. 

**Activity Tracked** : The comment author’s name, email address, and site URL (if provided during the comment submission) are stored in cookies. Learn more about these cookies. 

**Data Synced** : All data and metadata (see above) associated with comments. This includes the status of the comment and, if Akismet is enabled on the site, whether or not it was classified as spam by Akismet. 

## **Mobile Theme**  

**Data Used:**  A visitor’s preference on viewing the mobile version of a site. 

**Activity Tracked** : A cookie (akm_mobile) is stored for 3.5 days to remember whether or not a visitor of the site wishes to view its mobile version. Learn more about this cookie. 

## **Notifications**  

This feature is only accessible to registered users of the site who are logged in to WordPress.com. 

**Data Used:**  IP address, WordPress.com user ID, WordPress.com username, WordPress.com-connected site ID and URL, Jetpack version, user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code. Some visitor-related information or activity may be sent to the site owner via this feature. This may include: email address, WordPress.com username, site URL, email address, comment content, follow actions, etc. 

**Activity Tracked:**  Sending notifications (i.e. when we send a notification to a particular user), opening notifications (i.e. when a user opens a notification that they receive), performing an action from within the notification panel (e.g. liking a comment or marking a comment as spam), and clicking on any link from within the notification panel/interface. 

## **Protect**  

**Data Used:**  In order to check login activity and potentially block fraudulent attempts, the following information is used: attempting user’s IP address, attempting user’s email address/username (i.e. according to the value they were attempting to use during the login process), and all IP-related HTTP headers attached to the attempting user. 

**Activity Tracked** : Failed login attempts (these include IP address and user agent). We also set a cookie (jpp_math_pass) for 1 day to remember if/when a user has successfully completed a math captcha to prove that they’re a real human. Learn more about this cookie. 

**Data Synced** : Failed login attempts, which contain the user’s IP address, attempted username or email address, and user agent information. 

## **Search**  

**Data Used** : Any of the visitor-chosen search filters and query data in order to process a search request on the WordPress.com servers. 

## **Sharing**  

**Data Used** : When sharing content via email (this option is only available if Akismet is active on the site), the following information is used: sharing party’s name and email address (if the user is logged in, this information will be pulled directly from their account), IP address (for spam checking), user agent (for spam checking), and email body/content. This content will be sent to Akismet (also owned by Automattic) so that a spam check can be performed. Additionally, if reCAPTCHA (by Google) is enabled by the site owner, the sharing party’s IP address will be shared with that service. You can find Google’s privacy policy here. 

## **Simple Payments**  

This feature is only available to sites on the Premium and Professional plans, and the actual payment processing is handled by PayPal. 

**Data Used** : Transaction amount, transaction currency code, product title, product price, product ID, order quantity, PayPal payer ID, and PayPal transaction ID. 

**Activity Tracked:**  The PayPal payer ID, transaction ID, and HTTP referrer are sent with a payment completion tracking event that is attached to the site owner. 

**Data Synced** : PayPal transaction ID, PayPal transaction status, PayPal product ID, quantity, price, customer email address, currency, and payment button CTA text. 

Because payments are processed by PayPal, we recommend reviewing its privacy policy. 

**Subscriptions**  

**Data Used** : To initiate and process subscriptions, the following information is used: subscriber’s email address and the ID of the post or comment (depending on the specific subscription being processed). In the event of a new subscription being initiated, we also collect some basic server data, including all of the subscribing user’s HTTP request headers, the IP address from which the subscribing user is viewing the page, and the URI which was given in order to access the page (REQUEST_URI and DOCUMENT_URI). This server data used for the exclusive purpose of monitoring and preventing abuse and spam. 

**Activity Tracked** : Functionality cookies are set for a duration of 347 days to remember a visitor’s blog and post subscription choices if, in fact, they have an active subscription. 

## **WooCommerce** **  Services** 

**Data Used** : For payments with PayPal or Stripe: purchase total, currency, billing information. For taxes: the value of goods in the cart, value of shipping, destination address. For checkout rates: destination address, purchased product IDs, dimensions, weight, and quantities. For shipping labels: customer’s name, address as well as the dimensions, weight, and quantities of purchased products. 

**Data Synced:** For payments, we send the purchase total, currency and customer’s billing information to the respective payment processor. Please see the respective third party’s privacy policy (Stripe’s Privacy Policy?and?PayPal’s Privacy Policy) for more details. For automated taxes we send the value of goods in the cart, the value of shipping, and the destination address to TaxJar. Please see TaxJar’s?Privacy Policy?for details about how they handle this information. For checkout rates we send the destination ZIP/postal code and purchased product dimensions, weight and quantities to USPS or?Canada Post, depending on the service used. For shipping labels we send the customer’s name, address as well as the dimensions, weight, and quantities of purchased products to?EasyPost. We also store the purchased shipping labels on our server to make it easy to reprint them and handle support requests. 

## **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. 

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – ** [Privacy Policy ](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)**

## **Disqus** **  Commenting** 

Disqus is commenting software. **[Privacy Policy ](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy)**

## **Facebook** **  Analytics for Apps (** **Facebook** **, Inc.)**  

Facebook Analytics for Apps is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy ](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)**

## **Facebook** **  Like button and social widgets (** **Facebook** **, Inc.)**  

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [**Privacy Policy**  ](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

## **Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)**  

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy ](https://twitter.com/privacy)

## **Facebook** **  Analytics for Apps (** **Facebook** **, Inc.)**  

Facebook Analytics for Apps is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy ](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

## **YouTube V** **ideo widget (Google Inc.)**  

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy ](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)**

## **Drip newsletter marketing.**  

Drip is a newsletter marketing platform. 

Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy ](https://www.drip.com/privacy)**

## **Google Analytics for Firebase (Google Inc.)**  

Google Analytics for Firebase or Firebase Analytics is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. In order to understand Google’s use of Data, consult Google’s partner policy. 

Firebase Analytics may share Data with other tools provided by Firebase, such as Crash Reporting, Authentication, Remote Config or Notifications. The User may check this privacy policy to find a detailed explanation of the other tools used by the Owner. 

This Application uses identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID or Advertising Identifier for iOS, respectively) and technologies similar to cookies to run the Firebase Analytics service. 

Users may opt-out of certain Firebase features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Firebase related sections of this privacy policy, if available. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example) and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: USA – **[Privacy Policy ](https://policies.google.com/privacy)**

## **Business Partners and Other Third Parties**  

Through our Digital Properties, you are able to exercise choice with respect to certain data practices of companies participating in the choice tools we provide. When you exercise your choice, we may share some information collected from you, your computer, or your mobile device with these companies so that they may honor your requests concerning their data collection practices. Additionally, we may share information with service providers who may assist us in responding to your inquiries or requests, or otherwise perform some business or operational function for us. We may also disclose personal information about you if required to do so by law, including without limitation, by search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect our and third party rights, and for purposes disclosed at the time of collection. 

## **Links to Third Party Sites**  

Our Digital Properties may contain links to other websites operated by third parties we do not control and this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through our Digital Properties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites. 

## **Assignment**  

In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets or a bankruptcy, XiaomiToday may transfer your personally identifiable information to the new party in control or the party acquiring assets. Under such circumstances we would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this privacy policy, as it may be amended from time to time. Nevertheless, we cannot promise that an acquiring company or the merged company will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this privacy policy. 

## **Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations**  

In some cases, we may use or disclose your personally identifiable information to a third party if we are required to do so by law, or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law or legal process; to protect and defend our rights or to prevent misuse of our Sites; or to protect the personal safety of our employees, agents, partners, the users of the Sites, or the public. 

## **Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  

We may disclose or share individual, non-personally identifiable information and aggregate information in any manner other than that described herein that we deem appropriate or necessary. Among other things, we will disclose non-personally identifiable information to third parties to help us determine how people use parts of the Sites and who our users are so we can improve our Sites. We will also disclose non-personally identifiable information to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Sites. 

## **How d** **o the  ** **S** **ites  ** **u** **se  ** **c** **ookies and  ** **o** **ther  ** **t** **racking  ** **t** **echnologies?**  

Like many websites, we use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to record your preferences, track the use of our Websites and your exposure to our online advertisements. We may also use these technologies to monitor traffic, improve the Sites and make it easier and/or relevant for your use. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your web browser to decline cookies, some features of the Sites may not work or may not work as designed. 

We also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), on our Websites. Google Analytics uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Websites, compile reports on the Websites’ activity, and provide other services related to Websites activity and usage. 

The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The Websites do not use Google Analytics to gather information that personally identifies you. 

The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies. 

We may partner with third-party advertising companies to better provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These third party advertisers may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Sites. They may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content. 

These online advertising partners do not have access to or use your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information from us, without your consent. They may, however, use persistent identifiers to anonymously track your Internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond these Sites. While we restrict their further use of such information, such third parties may, with sufficient data from other sources, be able to personally identify you, unknown to us. 

Third-party ad serving companies and other unaffiliated advertisers also display advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer or utilize other data collection and tracking technologies, to collect information such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular advertisement. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies, how they may be used, or the information they may collect and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of those third parties. Please visit the sites of those businesses at the links above to review their privacy policies. We may add or change the list of third-party ad servers from time to time and we encourage you to check this section for changes. You can learn more about online advertising at **[www.aboutads.info/consumers](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers). **

Many of the third party advertisers that place tracking tools on our Websites are members of programs that offer you additional choices regarding the collection and use of your information. You can learn more about the options available to limit these third parties’ collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance, as well as the web pages for Facebook’s ad preferences tool and privacy policy. 

Similarly, you can learn about your options to opt-out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through your device settings. For more information about how to change these settings for Apple, Android or Windows devices, see: 

  * **Apple:  [http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4228](https://support.apple.com/kb/HT4228) **
  * **Android:[http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) **
  * **Windows:[http://choice.microsoft.com/en-US/opt-out ](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)**

Please note that opting-out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Websites or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. 

Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. Because a “Do Not Track” compliance protocol has not yet been finalized, XiaomiToday’s information collection and disclosure practices, and the choices that we provide to customers, will continue to operate as described in this privacy policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received. 

## **What Are Your Choices?**  

We believe you should have choices about the collection, use and sharing of your information. Although you cannot opt-out of all data collection when you visit our sites, you can limit the collection, use and sharing of your personally identifiable information. For information regarding your choices related to interest-based advertising, please see the “How do the Sites use cookies and other tracking technologies?” section above. 

## **Collection of personally identifiable information**  

All personally identifiable information is provided on a voluntary basis. If you do not want XiaomiToday to collect such information, you should not submit it to the Sites. However, doing so will restrict your ability to access some content and use some of the functionality of the sites. 

## **Emails and Newsletters**  

You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail marketing messages and newsletters from XiaomiToday by following the instructions contained within the emails and newsletters, or by e-mailing, calling or writing us at the addresses below. 

## **Governing Law**  

We attempt to protect the personally identifiable information of all users of our Sites and we attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to XiaomiToday’s services. If you are uncertain whether this privacy policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personally identifiable information to XiaomiToday. 

## **GDPR Compliance for European Territories**  

In compliance with European privacy laws, in particular, the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), XiaomiToday provides specific additional rights for citizens of the European Territories such as the right to access, rectification, and the right to object and complaint. Specifically: 

  * The right to request information about whether and which personal data is processed by us, and the right to demand that personal data is rectified or amended. 
  * Under certain circumstances, the right to request that personal data should be deleted. 
  * Under certain circumstances, the right to demand that the processing of personal data should be restricted. 
  * Withdraw your consent to the processing and use of your data completely or partially at any time with future application. 
  * Have the right to obtain your personal data in a common, structured and mechanically readable format. 
  * Contact our data protection officer if there are any questions, comments, complaints or requests in connection with our statement on data protection and the processing of your personal data.
  * The right to complain to the responsible supervisory authority if believed that the processing of your personal data is in violation of the legislation. 

In addition to the above, we reference certain rights for European Territory citizens throughout this Privacy Policy. Pursuant to the GDPR, citizens from “European Territories” mean the European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the term “European Territories” shall continue to include the United Kingdom, even after the United Kingdom leaves the European Economic Area following Brexit. 

Please email **xiaomitoday@gmail.com** with the subject line “GDPR Request” for any questions about exercising any of the above rights. 

## **Other Important Information**  

### **How Your Information Is Secured**  

We take reasonable security measures to protect your information, including the use of physical, technical and administrative controls. Please understand, however, that while we try our best to safeguard your personally identifiable information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. You need to help protect the privacy of your own information. You must take precautions to protect the security of any personally identifiable information that you may transmit over any home networks, wireless routers, wireless (WiFi) networks or similar devices by using encryption and other techniques to prevent unauthorized persons from intercepting or receiving any of your personally identifiable information. You are responsible for the security of your information when using unencrypted, open access or otherwise unsecured networks.   

The time period for which we keep information varies according to the purpose for which it is used for. In some cases, there are legal requirements to keep data for a minimum period. Unless there is a specific legal requirement for us to keep the information, we will retain it for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected or for which it is to be further processed. 

### **Children’s Information**  

The Sites are not intended for children under 16 years of age. XiaomiToday does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16 years of age. If you are under 16 years of age, do not provide personal information to XiaomiToday without providing us with consent from your parents. If XiaomiToday discovers that a child under the age of 16 has provided XiaomiToday with personal information and we do not have parental consent, XiaomiToday will immediately delete that child’s information from the Sites. 

If you believe that the company has been provided with the personal information of a child under the age of 16 without parental consent, please notify us immediately at **xiaomitoday@gmail.com.**

### **Your California Privacy Rights**  

XiaomiToday does not disclose your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosures. 

### **Questions  ** **about** **  this Policy or Access to Your Information** 

You may use the contact information provided to request access or changes to your personally identifiable information; however, you will not be permitted to examine the personally identifiable information of any other person or entity and may be required to provide us with personally identifiable information to verify your identity prior to accessing any records containing information about you. We may not accommodate a request to change or delete personally identifiable information if we believe doing so would violate any law or legal requirement, or cause the information to be incorrect.
